------------------OP-----------------------------
------------------ED-----------------------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------
樱律联萌站 http://bbs.ylbud.com/
So, how does it feel to be helpless
against the flames consuming you?
どうだ
手も足も出ずに炎に焼かれる気分
樱律联萌站为您带来高质量中日双语字幕
Sire.
魔王様
中日双语字幕由 樱律字幕组 制作
Your flesh, your entrails...
I'll devour you down to the very bone
貴様らの肉、腸、骨に至るまで
感谢以下成员倾情制作
听译：五月、吉禾　校对：jez　时间轴：咲夜　后期：OMG
この俺が食らい尽くし
to feed my own ambition!
わが野望の勝手としてくれよ
Sire, listen to me...
いえ、ですから、魔王様
Come, the feast begins! The first
sacrifice offered to me shall be...
さぁ、宴の始まりだ
俺に捧げられる行けに第一号は
...you!
貴様だ
Sire!
魔王様
What, Ashiya?
何だよ、芦屋
Please dine a bit more quietly.
You're disturbing the people around us.
お食事はもうすこしお静かになさってください
周りのお客さんに迷惑です
Sorry. I got a little overexcited.
すまん、ちょっとテンション上がりすぎだ
Gotta say, though, beef
intestines are really good!
しかし、ホルモンで本当にうまいよな
For the first time, I understand those
demons who say entrails are tasty!
腸うまいっていう悪魔達の気持ちが初めて分かったよ
How nice to hear, Sire.
それはよろしゅうございました
But please eat your vegetables, too.
Or your diet will be unbalanced.
が、肉だけでなく
野菜も召し上がってください
栄養バランスが偏ります
Lighten up. We're celebrating my promotion here.
そう言うこと言うな
今日は昇進祝いの外食だ
Oh, hey, maybe we should buy
dinner for Urushihara on our way home.
そういえば、さぁ
漆原の晩飯買ってちょっといいんじゃねえ
I bet they have yakiniku takeout boxes.
焼き肉弁当とかあるぽづ
Not necessary.
必要ありません
Apparently he learned "online shopping"
recently, and he's wrecking our budget.
最近漆原はネットショッピング名で物を覚えたらしく
家計を無駄に使い込みすぎっているのです
I ask you to bring down
the hammer on him, Sire.
裁きの鉄槌お願い致します
Kono shunkan, kono basho ga sutaato
この瞬間
在这瞬间
この場所がスダート
这里就是起点
Imeeji shite miyou nani ga dekiru no ka na
イメージして見よう
试着想象一下
何ができるのかな
我能做些什么
Shinjirarenai dekigoto datte aru
信じられない出来事だってある
会发生些不可思议的事吧
Motto... koete yukeru ne
もっと超えて行けるね
克服一切走的更远
Zero kara umareru subete kagayaite ano sora e
ゼロから生まれるすべて輝いて
从零重生的一切都特别耀眼
FLYあの空へ
翱翔朝着那片天空
Omoikiri habatakitai
思い切り羽ばたきたい
想尽情地展翅
Saikou no sumairu de warainagara saa yukou!
最高のスマイルで笑いながら
以最完美的笑容
さぁ、行く
笑着前行吧
Michi no sekai e to ima tobidasou yo
未知の世界へと　今飛び出そうよ
奔向未知的世界仿佛就要飞出来
Mirai wo erabi, kimeru no wa jibun
未来を選び決めるのは自分
自己决定自己的未来
Yume wo oikakete yukou
夢を追いかけて行　こう泣く日をある
追逐着梦想前进　也会有哭泣的日子
Naku hi mo aru
Sore wa daiji na negai, kienaide
それは大事な願い消えないで
珍贵的愿望不会消失
Kitto aeru kara, asu no kimi e...
きっと会えるから
一定可以再次遇
明日の君
朝着未来的你
"The Devil is a Part-Timer!"
The Devil Climbs the Stairway to School
You say Olba is missing?
Yes. It seems the hero Emilia
is still alive in the other world.
What?
That's not all.
The Devil appears to be as well.
Th-The Devil, too?!
Olba said that he faded away
along with the Better Half
after a fierce battle at the Devil's Castle.
A downright lie.
I believe Father Olba was also
behind Emerada and Albert's capture.
What?
We've confirmed that Emerada has
returned to the Holy Saint Aire Empire.
I received a report that
she's spreading word
of Emilia's survival and Father
Olba's apostasy.
A-Apostasy? A high priest,
branded an apostate?!
Father Robertio, please stay calm!
Try not to make such shocking reports here.
But it is the truth.
We can't ignore the influence it will have
for Saint Aire's Court Celestialist to
formally acknowledge Emilia's survival.
And it contradicts the Church's
official pronouncement of her death.
What shall we do, Father?
Wh-What do you mean?
Acknowledge that a high priest turned apostate,
or liquidate all three:
Emerada, Albert, and Emilia?
That's absurd!
Aren't you the ones who have
been instructing the Inquisition
to commit such absurdities?
Then what about you? What would you do?
Villa Rosa
Sasazuka
We're home!
帰ったぞ
You're late! I'm hungry!
遅い、お腹減った
How about you be polite and
say "Welcome home, Master"?
「お帰りなさいます、ご主人様」くらい
言ったら、どうだ
It's thanks to His Majesty's benevolence
that you're allowed to live here.
魔王様のお慈悲で
この部屋に住まわせてやっているのだ
Here, present for you.
ソラ、漆原、お土産だ
Hey! I thought you two went to a yakiniku place!
ちょっと、二人共焼肉屋行ったんじゃなかったの
What's the big idea, bringing me
a pork bowl from Sugiya?!
スキ屋の豚丼でどういうこと
We prepared that computer and
internet environment for you.
貴様にはそのパソコンとインターネット環境
整えやっただろう
How much do you think
that cost? So don't complain.
どれだけの出費だっと思ってる
文句言うな
I can't eat the computer!
食べられないでしょう、パソコンは
Then gather information on existing
magic in this world for His Majesty.
だったら、魔王様のためにこの世界に現存する
魔力に関する情報の収集をしろ
Depending on your success,
その成果に応じて
I'll upgrade you to a large-sized
pork bowl, or even a jumbo-sized one.
豚丼も並から大盛り
そして特盛りになる
Jumbo pork is all I get for success?!
成果出しても特盛り
Hey, Urushihara, are you honestly
good at this computer stuff?
だけどよ漆原
お前本当にパソコン何で使いこなせるのか
Chaos Crossing: Doom Forest ~No Escape~
If you don't believe me,
I'll show you my skills right now.
信用できないなら
僕の腕を見せてやるよ
Come on, it's almost the end of my shift...
もう終業間業に
Thank you for calling the
Docodemo Customer Service Center.
お電話ありがとうございます
dokodemoお客様電話相談室
My name is Yusa...
担当遊佐うかが致します
Wow, you got through!
You're right, Urushihara, you're amazing!
繋がった
本当だ、漆原、すげぇ
Huh?
は？
Hey, Emi! Can you hear us?
おい、恵美、聞こえるか
M-Maou...
ま、真奥
What do you think you're doing?
I'm working right now!
一体何のつもり
私まだ仕事中なんですけど
Aw, don't be mad. This is a hacking experiment.
そう怒るな
ハキングの実験だ
Urushihara said he could do all
kinds of stuff if he had a computer,
漆原がパソコンあれば
いろいろできるって言うから
so I made my first big
credit card purchase on installment.
クレジットカードの分割ばらいで
初めて高価な買い物したんだけどよ
I have several questions right now,
but first off, who's Urushihara?!
いろいろと聞きたいことはあるけど
まず、誰、漆原って
That's Lucifer.
ルシフェルのことだよ
Hey! What do you mean, Lucifer?!
Don't tell me he's in the Devil's Castle with...
ちょっと、ルシフェルってどういうことよ
まさか、魔王城にルシフェル
Bye! Sorry for interrupting.
じゃ、邪魔して悪かった
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございました
You're amazing, Mr. Maou!
すごいですね、真奥さん
I can't believe you're already
shift manager after less than a year!
バート入って一年も経たないつちに
時間帯責任者って
Really? Well, I'm just a substitute for
the boss when she isn't here, though.
そうか
まぁ、店長いない時間だけの
店長代理だけどな
But doesn't it mean even if it's only
a couple of people for a limited time,
でも、それでつまり
時間帯限定で例え僅かな人数とはいえ
you get to rule over humans?
人間を支配できるってこと
I won't allow it.
させないわよ
Emi?!
恵美
Welcome to MgRonald's!
いらっしゃいませ
I need to talk to you.
話があるんだけど
As you can see, I'm working. Let it wait.
見ての通りの勤務中だ
後にしてくれ
You started it with your weird
phone call while I was working.
勤務中に侵しなんで
電話かけてきたのはそっちが先でしょう
U-Um, may I interest you in some
jalapeño fries? They're our featured item!
あの、よろしいければ
ただいま、キャンペーン期間中のアンノペンポテトはいかがですか
This thing doesn't really have
the specs for online gaming...
やっば、このスペックだとネットゲームはきびしいよな
Blah, I wanna play a game.
ゲームやりたい
東京近郊恐怖スポット！！渋谷区編
"Scary Spots in the Tokyo Suburbs!!
Shibuya Edition"
Isn't this?
これって
"100 Mysteries of Super-Ancient Ruins"
"Cappadocia"...
カパトキヤ（位于土耳其地区，在此修建了很多的教堂、修道院和避难所）
"It is not impossible that
this site is the former home
これはかつてこの地に落ちた下級悪魔の住居跡
of a lower-level demon who fell to Earth."
という可能性もなきにしも在らず
Villa Rosa
Sasazuka
If that's true, we may be able
to replenish our magic there...
もし、そうってあれば
魔力を補給することもできるやもしれなが
But who knows how many months' worth
of His Majesty's wages it would take
しかしトルコまでの旅費となると
魔王様の給料一体何ヶ月分になるのか
to fund a trip to Turkey?
It's from the landlady?
大家さんから
Good night!
お疲れ様でした
So what do you want, Emi?
って、何だよ、恵美
Like you don't know! What was
with that phone call yesterday?!
「何だよ」じゃなくて
何なのよ、昨日の電話
I already told you, that was Urushihara.
だから、漆原だって言ったじゃねぇか
And why is Lucifer "Urushihara" now?
何でルシフェルが漆原なのよ
The police arrested Olba,
after all. He's gotta lay low.
あれから、オルバは警察に捕まっちまうし
アイツも浮かずに出あるかね
For lack of a better option, I decided
to put him up at my place for a while.
しようがないから
しばらく家で面倒を見ることにしたんだよ
Apartments for Rent
Villa Rosa Sasazuka
10 Square Meters of Tatami
Three men in that tiny place?
男３人なの狭い部屋で
Got a problem with that?!
悪いか
What choice do I have?
I'm pretty much out of magic.
しかたねぇだろう
俺の魔力はもうほとんとすっかり残るんだ
We can't go back to Ente Isla even if we want to.
エンテイスラには帰りたくても帰れない
Hmph! Well, I could go home any time I wanted.
まぁ、私の方はいつても帰れるけどね
And I don't have to slave away
これからはゲート制限の為に
looking for a source of celestial
force to control the Gate.
聖法気回復の手段をアクセス探す必要もないし
Then why don't you hurry up and go home?
だったら、とっとと帰ればいいじゃねぇか
I-I'm a hero!
私は勇者よ
As long as you're in Japan, I have
a duty to stay and keep tabs on you!
貴方は日本にいるかぎり
ここで貴方を見張る義務があるの
Man, what a pain.
面倒臭い
Sadao
Maou
Shiro
Ashiya
Yo, I'm home.
おい、帰ったぞ
Urushihara?!
漆原、しっかりしろう
Hang in there! Who did this to you?!
誰にやられた
S-Sire...
ま、魔王様
You mustn't... look at that!
それを見てはいけません
A photo of the landlady in a swimsuit?
大家の水着写真？
Yes. She said she's visiting Hawaii,
はい、ハワイに滞在中とのことって
and she enclosed a photo of herself
frolicking in the waves at Waikiki Beach...
ワイキキビーチで波と玉売れる写真と同封されており
It's unbelievable!
信じられないよ
How could she show us that?!
You gotta censor that stuff!
何でものみせるんだよ
きちんと検閲しなきゃ駄目だろう
あんなの
You're pathetic. What kind of demon
freaks out over something like that?
情けねぇ
悪魔がそんなのに怯えってどうするんだよ
Fine, you look, then!
だったら真奥も見てみるよ
More importantly, Urushihara,
have you gathered info on Earth's magic?
それより、漆原
魔力に関する情報は集まったのか
Hey, you just pulled a fast one!
You did, didn't you, Maou?!
混ました、真奥今混ましだよね
His Majesty certainly did not "pull a fast one."
魔王様は混してなどいない
Sometimes a valiant retreat is called for.
時に勇気ある撤退も必要なのだ
"Valiant retreat," my butt.
何が勇気ある撤退だよ
But whatever. I just found something interesting.
でも、まぁいいや
ちょうと一つ
気になる情報見けだとこだったん
"Scary Spots in the Tokyo Suburbs!!"
How does that qualify as
information about magic?
それのどこが魔力関する情報なのだ
The magical spots in this world
この世界の魔力スポットって
aren't all ancient ruins like
the pyramids and Stonehenge.
何ピラミッドや石丼辺陣みたいの古代遺跡だけじゃない
If you look, you can find a whole bunch right nearby.
探せば近場にもたくさんある
Mysteries of
the Pyramids
You can't find that info at the library, though.
もっともそういう情報は図書館で得られない
This might be the best candidate in the area.
この近くだっと言う多量区なりかな
"The Seven Wonders of Sasahata North High School"
"The Jet Geezer of Koshu Kaido Road"
A sealed classroom?
開かずの教室？
Yep. There's a disused classroom
in this place's old schoolhouse,
そう、ここの旧校舎に
今使われない教室があるそうなんだけど
and supposedly every night
よほど囁き声や笑い声
you can hear whispers and laughter
and footsteps echoing in there.
足音が響きったりするんったりって
If you ask me, there's
probably a demon involved.
僕の見立てだと
これは魔の物が関わっている可能性が高い
Sasahata North High School
Is this the school?
ここがその学校か
It's cheerier than I expected.
Do you think there's really a magical spot here?
以外と明るい感じですね
本当にこの中に魔力に関わる場所があるのでしょうか
ここからじゃ特に何も感じないけどな
I don't really sense anything from out here...
I believe it will be difficult for
outsiders like us to get in, though.
いずれにせよ、部外者であるわれわれが
勝手に校内に入るのは難しいそうですね
Mr. Maou!
真奥さん
Miss Sasaki?!
佐々木さん
Huh, I thought I recognized the
name of this school. So it's Chi's.
何だ、どこかで聞いたことある学校名だと思った
ちーちゃんの学校だったのか
Hey, Sasa-chii, is he the one from MgRonald's?
ささち、ひょっとしてマクドナルドの
Yes! It's Mr. Maou!
そう、真奥さん
Who's the other guy?
もう一人の方はネームメートの芦屋さん
Mr. Ashiya, his roommate.
ネームメート
Roommate?!
六畳人前のアパートで男二人の倹しい区らしい
Two men living frugally in a little
one-room apartment! Do they share a futon?!
布団は一つ？
N-No, wrong idea!
Kao, quit randomly imagining things!
違う、違う、佳织何勝手想像してるのよ
She seems to be enjoying her conversation...
but what on Earth is it about?
何やら楽しげに話されているようですが
一体どうの話を
開かずの教室ですか
A sealed classroom?
Yeah. I heard it's one of
your school's "seven wonders."
そう、ちーちゃんの高校の七不思議の一つに
そういうのがあるって聞いたんだけどさ
Sure, that story's famous.
確かにその話は有名ですよ
開かずの教室の中から
People say they hear monsters groaning,
怪物の呻き声が聞こえてきたとか
窓に悪魔の姿が映ったとか
or see demons reflected on the windows...
Oh! Was that you, Mr. Maou?
まさか、その正体は真奥さんだったとか
No, it wasn't.
いや、俺じゃないから
But it might have something to do with Ente Isla,
でも、ましかしたら
エンテイスラが関係しているかもしれないだが
so I thought I'd check it out.
それでちょっと調べようと思って
Understood, Mr. Maou!
In that case, leave it to me!
分かりました、真奥さん
そういうことなら
私に任せてください
The old schoolhouse is this way!
こちが旧校舎です
But why did that room become
the "sealed classroom"?
しかし　なぜそこが開かずの教室に
あくまでうわさなんですけど
This is just what I've heard,
but they say that way before I was born,
私が生まれるずっと前
a student disappeared from it,
almost like he was spirited away,
その教室で
生徒が神隠しみたいに消えた事件があったらしくて
and it's never been used since.
それ以来ずっと使われないそうです
Hey, want to take a little
break now and have a snack?
あっ　この辺でちょっと休憩して
お菓子食べますか
Miss, this isn't a field trip.
いえ、遠足でありませんので
千ちゃん　なんか楽しそうだな
You seem like you're having fun, Chi.
だってバイトでもなんでも
Sure, because at work or not,
I'm always the one getting your help.
いつもあたし真奥さんに
助けられてばっかりだったから
So I'm happy that I can help you!
真奥さんに役に立てるなら
うれしいんです
You're not scared?
怖くないのか
Not if you're with me...
真奥さんが一緒だから
Oh. So, this "seven wonders" thing.
What are the other six?
そっか
で　七不思議っていうけど
ほかにどんなのがあるんだ
ああ　ええと
Um...
The north stairway with a different
number of steps going up than going down.
登ったときと降りたときの段数が違う　北階段
The statue of Kinjiro Ninomiya
that walks around covered in blood.
血まみれで歩く二宮金次郎ぞ
The sculpture in the art room that
gets a fold in its eyelid at three a.m.
午前三時になるとふたいま仏塔に美術室の彫像
The dictionary in the library where
the words for "curse" are stained red.
呪いって言葉だけ赤く塗りつぶされた
図書室に広辞苑
The piano in the music room where B
sometimes won't play. B for blood...
時々siの音だけならなくなる
音楽室のピアノ
開かずの教室とあわせて六つしかありませんが
Those plus the sealed classroom only make six...
Nobody knows the seventh one.
七つ目は誰も知らないんです
Because if someone learns all seven, then...
なぜなら
七つ全部知ってしまうと
Then?
知ってしまうと？
Th-Then what?
なん、なんなんだ？
He gets a call on his cell from
the afterworld, and it steals his soul!
あの世から携帯に電話がかかってきて
"Incoming Call"
魂を持っていかれちゃうから
But isn't that just unreasonable?!
それはどう考えても理不尽じゃねー
何で知ったなけりゃ魂もってかれんだ？
Why would just finding out get your soul stolen?!
What if it was a coincidence that you found out?!
たまたま偶然したったら
どうすんだ？
魔王様　落ち着いてください
Sire, please calm down.
Think about it: why would
the story about this room,
そもそも佐々木さんが生まれる前からあるという
which existed long before Miss Sasaki
was born, involve a cell phone?
開かずの教室の七不思議の話に
なぜ携帯電話が出てくるんですか？
Good point?!
確かに
"Urushihara"
- What the hell, Urushihara?! Don't startle me!
- What are you shouting for?
何だよ漆原
びっくりさせんなよ
何大声だしてんのさ
どう？開かずの間には着いた
Well? Did you make it to the sealed room?
Not yet! Why are you even calling?!
まだだよ
っすが何のようだよ
Just FYI, I think that room is probably
somewhere the Gate once opened in.
因みにだけど
その開かずの教室って
多分過去にゲートが
開いたことがある場所だと思うんだよね
ゲートが？
The Gate?
Yeah. Once the Gate opens someplace,
magnetic fields there destabilize
そう
一度ゲートが開いた場所っていうのは
磁場が不安定になって
and it's easier for the Gate to open there again.
その後ゲートが開きやすくなるんだよ
Then the story about the
student getting spirited away...
じゃひょっとして
昔神隠しになって生徒がいるのは
It's highly likely he was sucked into the Gate.
ゲートに飲み込まれた可能性が高いね
Anyway, if we can manage to
be there next time it opens,
まとにかく
今度ゲートが開いた瞬間に
うまく言わせられれば
そこから魔力を補給できるかもしれないし
maybe we can get some magic through it.
Lemme know when you get there. Bye.
開かずの間に着いたらまた連絡して
それじゃ
それにしてもルシフェルあのやつ
That Urushihara... How did he find out so much?
一体どうやってそんなことまで調べたのでしょう
The internet is really something!
やっぱインターネットスゲー
いま　音がしてんの？
You guys heard that sound, right?
警備員しょうか
A guard, perhaps?
They should all have left by now.
この時間はいないはずです
So, a demon who came through
the Gate from another world?
ゲートよりきたりし
ふん　異世界の魔物か
Knowing that ahead of time
means it ain't scary. Bring it on!
最初からソート分かっていれば
怖くネイ
受けて絶つぜ
Do you have enough magic left to fight, Sire?
戦えるほどの魔力は残っているのですか？
If worst comes to worst, use this.
いざというときはこれを
What's that?
なんだそれ？
A talisman. It's already proven
effective against demons like us.
魔よけです
その効果は我々悪魔が血潮する
Isn't that the landlady's letter?
ってそれ大家の。。。
Footsteps...
足音
What do you mean by bringing
a high school girl here after dark?
夜の学校に女子高生に連れて込んで何をするつもり
Emi?!
エミ？！
なるほど
I see, so you were plotting to get
magic from that sealed classroom.
その開かずの教室から
魔力を得ようと企んでいたってわけね
More like, what are you
doing at a school this late?
っすがお前こんな夜の中に学校で何してんだよ
Is the hero trespassing?
勇者が不法侵入か
U-Um, I'm sorry, but you're not
allowed to wear shoes in the building.
あ、あのすみません
構内は土足検診なので
Would you change into these?
これに履き替えてもらいませんか
I was tailing you and I saw you
sneaking into a school after hours,
あなたたちの後につけていたら
夜の学校で忍び込んでいくのが見えたから
so I came in after you, that's all.
追いかけてきただけ
Anyway, I'm coming with you.
I can't just roll over and let you get more mag...
とにかく　私も同行させてもらうわよ
ここで大目を見たあなた達
魔力を補給させるわけには行かないから
Argh, Maou!
って魔王！！
Mr. Maou, is it really okay
to leave Miss Yusa behind?
いいんですか真奥さん
遊佐さん置いてきちゃって
Totally. She's nothing but trouble.
いいんだよ
あいつが絡むどのぐらいのことならネイ
Hold right there, Maou!
待ちなさい魔王！！
ああもうめんどくせい
- Ugh, what a pain!
- Don't you run from me! I'll kick you!
Maou! Don't you run from me! I'll kick you!
うん　どうした千ちゃん？
What's wrong, Chi?
I-It's nothing.
なん、なんでもありません
There you are, monster!
出たわね化け物
Okay!
よし
Not okay, you freakin' moron!
よくねいよ馬鹿野郎
Oh, Miss Yusa, that's called an
"anatomical model," and it's just a doll!
ああ遊佐さん
それ人体模型っていってただの人形です
Huh?!
へえ？
I'd wager Emilia is the only
hero in the whole universe
聖剣で人体模型をばらばらにした勇者は
世界広してよどエミリアくらいでしょうね
to ever chop up an anatomical
model with a sacred sword.
Do normal heroes bust out their
sacred swords and attack like that?!
いきなり聖剣で切りかかるかふつう
貴様　これを何とかしとけよ
Do something about this, woman.
These things've gotta be expensive.
Well, don't come to me for help.
こういうのって高いだろう
ああ俺知らネイ
Th-They'll never know if we don't say anything.
黙ってれば分かりません
なんてもちろんだめですね
But of course that's out of the question, right?
I-It's your fault for sneaking
in here to begin with!
もともといえば
あんたたちは学校に忍び込んだのは悪いでしょう
You're a sore loser, Emilia.
お嬢きばかりだなエミリア
Use your magic to fix it!
魔力で何とかしなさいよ
Why should I have to use my
precious magic to cover your butt?
何でお前の結を俺の貴重な魔力で
ふかわねばならねいんだ
この模型　心臓がひとつしかない
This model only has one heart!
Mr. Ashiya, I don't know about demons,
but humans only ever have one!
アシアさん　悪魔はどうか知らないけど
人間の心臓はひとつですから
So, the sealed classroom is at
the other end of this passageway.
この向こうに開かずの教室があるのね
Look, just keep the sacred sword sheathed.
いいから聖剣しまってろう
俺がいいというまで出すな
Don't take it out until I say.
I don't take orders from you.
あなたに指図されるいわれはないわ
この向こうは旧校舎です
That's the old schoolhouse there.
The sealed classroom is on the
third floor, all the way up the stairs.
開かずの教室は
階段登って一番上　三階です
Okay. Let's go.
よし　行くぞ
This is the sealed classroom...
ここが開かずの教室
I don't remember it being boarded up, though...
でもこんな板　打ち付けられてかな
I told you, put the sword away!
だから聖剣しまえって
What is it, Mr. Ashiya?
どうしたんですかアシアさん
このドア
There are signs of someone
using this door recently.
最近誰か手いりした跡がある
They're not attached...
固定されてない
So this door wasn't sealed after all?
開かずな扉じゃなかったってこと
It feels strangely lived-in.
なんか妙に生活観があるな
It certainly doesn't look like
it's been sealed shut for years.
とても長い間開かずの教室だったと見えませんね
あ？あれは？
What's that?
A game system?
ゲーム機？
"Urushihara"
What now, Urushihara?!
なんだよ漆原？
Are you there yet?
そろそろ開かずの教室に着いたわ
We just got here.
今ついたとこだよ
なんだよいちいち電話かけてくんなよ
What's with you? Quit calling every
five seconds! You're startling me!
びっくりするだろう
そこに何か落ちてない？
Do you see anything on the floor?
Like, say... a game system?
たとえば　ゲーム機とか？
Yep, it's here. We have it right now.
落ちてるよ
いま手に持ってるよ
ああ　やっぱりそこに落ちてるか
So I was right, that was where it got left.
- You were "right"?
- Huh?
やっぱり？
えっ？いやなんでもない
Oh, no, nothing!
Would you mind bringing that home for me?
悪いけど　それもってかえってきてくれる？
Urushihara. Don't tell me you...
漆原　お前ひょっとして
Hmm? What?
うん?何？
You said this was an easy
place for the Gate to open.
ゲートが開きやすい場所とかいってたけど
Did you and Olba open the
Gate here to come to Japan?
オルバとお前ここにゲートを開いて
日本に来たのか？
Yeah, we did. Didn't I mention that?
そうだよ　いってなかったっけ
No, you did not!
いってネイよ！！
そこでしばらくそこでオルバと生活してたんだけどさ
So, I lived there with Olba for a while,
and I accidentally left the
game I was playing there...
そのとき遊んだゲームそこにおいてきちゃったから
Urushihara. You better not have
just sent us to bring back your game.
漆原　お前まさかこれ俺たちに拾ってこさせるつもりで
Of course not!
そんなわけじゃないか
I thought maybe the Gate opened again
and someone else came through, you know?
その後ゲートが開いて
誰が来たりしないかなと思ったから
でなんて見つけた？
So, did you find anything?!
If not, hurry back! I'm hungry!
見つけないなら早く帰ってきてよ
僕腹減っちゃった
あ豚丼で豚丼で
U-Um, a pork bowl would be totally fine!
Who does that Urushihara think he is?!
ったく漆原やつ調子に乗りあがって
このゲーム機
Why don't we sell this for cash at BookOn?
仏工乳でお金に変えてしまうのがどうでしょう
It would supplement our living expenses.
生活費も足しになります
どこまでせこいのよ
How miserly are you?
うん？
"Udon"
Udon?
うどん？
ったく昨日草臥れ儲けだったぜ
Dang it, yesterday was a waste of effort!
あ？
Oh, Mr. Maou! I found that
on the floor of the science...
ああ真奥さん
それ理科室に落ちてたんですけ。。
真奥さん？
Mr. Maou?! Wake up, Mr. Maou!
しっかりしてください
真奥さん！！
Give that back! It belongs to me!
返せよ　それ僕のなんだから
Only one hour of gaming per day!
You just be glad it didn't get sold at BookOn!
ゲームは一日一時間
物故に売られなかっただけでもありがたく覚え
誰か引っ越してきたか
Did somebody move in?
Watch out!
A-Are you okay?
だ、大丈夫か
魔王様大丈夫ですか
Sire! Are you all right?!
い、いや
Th-This girl just sort of
fell on me all of a sudden...
なんかこの子が急に落ちてきて
Carelessness is... the greatest enemy...
油断大敵。。。
はあ？
What?!
一二三四
どこから朝になる
从何处开始是清晨
Doko kara asa ni naru? Shizuka na sora
静かな空
安静的天空
見ないふりをした指きり
装作没看见的拉钩
Minai furi wo shita yubikiri koyubi no saki
恋日の先笑われた
恋爱之前被嘲笑
Warawareta tsuki nara kiete
yuku n da kinou no houkaku e
つきなら  消えてゆくんだ
就算是月亮 也会要消失
昨日の方角
向着昨天的方向
うそつき　臆病者
胆小的人　说谎精
Usotsuki okubyoumono
minna matomete boku nara
みんなまとめて　  僕なら　最低言ったのは
大家总结的这些　　我的话   就说声差劲
Saite ita no wa yume no naka da
夢の中だ
在梦中
月の影に隠してた
藏在月影中
Tsuki no kage ni kakushiteta
hontou wa ne naiteta
本当はね　泣いていだ
其实正在哭泣
Namida wa mou nagarenai karete shimatta no?
涙はもう流れない
眼泪已经不再流
枯れてしまうたな
枯竭了吧
Nani mo ka mo yurusetara
nagareru ka mo shirenai kedo
何もかも許せたら
虽然什么都原谅的话
流れるかもしれないけど
眼泪可能还是会流出来
Mamoritai mono bakari da na
守りたいものばかりだなあ
全都是想要守护的东西
The Devil's Budget Is Saved by Neighborliness